

EMMA BINDI

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Enthusiastic, self-starting and dedicated full stack developer.

Currently undertaking a full-time Bootcamp at CoderAcademy in Melbourne, building proficiency in front and back-end programming languages and concepts.

A cheerful and kind individual with strong communication skills and an energising can-do attitude.

I bring a wealth of experience in finance, procurement and project administration. Possess meticulous attention to detail and well-developed time management skills.

I take initiative wherever I work, proactively identify problems and opportunities, deliver accurate and complete work fast, and contribute to the culture and people around me.

Motivated to constantly develop my skills and grow personally as well as professionally. I have a knack for learning new software and solving problems.

EDUCATION

DIPLOMA OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Feb 2020 - Aug 2020 | Academy of Information Tech (VIC) Awarded "Women in Tech" Scholarship

BACHELOR OF COMMERCE: ACCOUNTING

June 2011 | Curtin University (WA)

CONNECT

PORTFOLIO

emma-bindi-portfolio.netlify.app

LINKEDIN

www.linkedin.com/in/emma-bindi

GITHUB

github.com/emmabindi

EMAIL | PHONE

emma.bindi@outlook.com | 0404 606 182

SKILLS

JavaScript HTML SASS

MongoDB Express React Node.js

Ruby Rails Git

EXPERIENCE

CONTRACT ADMINISTRATOR

NG Energy Jun 2019 - Feb 2020

Deliver administration for nationwide solar installation projects. Achieving safety, legislative and reporting compliance.

Championed the setup and roll out of Go Canvas Platform, to digitise the extensive library of paper forms.

PURCHASING OFFICER

Shark Bay Salt

Dec 2016 - Jun 2019

Provision of holistic purchasing and logistics services for remote mine sites. Managing competing priorities and customer satisfaction. Implementing automation of administrative tasks.

Member of processes & documentation improvement committee. Heavily involved in design and testing of Pronto accounting system updates and form overhaul in conjunction with IT dept.

Nominated as 1 of 4 (in >200 staff) as Pronto SME to provide first point of call support and training

PROJECT ASSISTANT & FINANCE ALL ROUNDER

BallPoint Construction

Apr 2015 - Dec 2016

Executed broad range of project support and accounting functions. Led business through technical transition from MYOB to Xero including chart of accounts setup & junior clerk training

TAXATION ACCOUNTANT

Marlston Taxation | Ernst & Young

2010 - 2015

Financial reporting and tax compliance for various entity structures including SMSF. Tax calculations, cashflow forecasting and general ledger reconciliations.

Proven ability to work with deadlines and display meticulous attention to detail

Implemented use of new software: BGL Simple Fund.

REFERENCES

CHRIS DALMAN - Project Director

0403 738 347 | NG Energy

ANDREW BARNES - Procurement Manager

0439 351 723 | Shark Bay Salt